healcure.org 2017-09-22

# Privacy Policy - Heal Cure

This private policy was made on the January 10, 2015 and is effective as from February 1, 2015.

This private policy is between The Heal Cure Organization., the owner of  **healcure.org  **website, thereafter referred to as “We”, and our esteemed readers who thereafter will be referred as to “You”.

### Content We Publish On this Site

All the content we publish in his website is  **ORIGINAL**  and has not been published elsewhere in full or parts. See our [ **Copyright**](http://healcure.org/about-us/copyright/ "Copyright"). The content is solely owned by The Heal Cure Organization. We reserve the sole right to modify, edit or remove any information, which does not meet the The Heal Cure Organization Standards.

### Copyright Protection

All the content contained on this website and any other website that belongs to The Heal Cure Organization, is copyright and cannot be reproduced fully or in parts in any material both digital and non-digital for whatsoever reason. It could however be shared retaining its original link without publishing it anywhere whether in books, websites, magazines or any other mass communication media. ©healcure.org 2015-2020.

Personal Information

The Heal Cure Organization does not collect any private information of our visitors for any reasons.

### Cookies and 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

[separator headline=”h3″ title=”Content in the Website”]All the content in this website is suitable for people for all family view. It has been written to comply to the [ **Terms and Conditions of Google AdSense**](https://www.google.com/adsense/localized-terms)

### Merger or Bankruptcy

In the event that we acquire, are acquired by, or merge with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign all collected information as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy or similar situation, we may not be able to control how your information is treated, transferred, or used.

### Changes and Updates

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. Any changes will be reflected by the effective date at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any current revisions.

### Contact Information

If you have any issue you would like to communicate to us concerning this private policy feel free [contact us](http://www.healcure.org/about-us/contact-us/).
